[BLANK_AUDIO]
Okay, if you are ready, let's continue here.
Are you all ready?
>> Yes, please.
>> Okay, so these are the tips for your final assessment.
[BLANK_AUDIO]
So, I think your final assessment is scheduled next Saturday or
Sunday, right?
[BLANK_AUDIO]
Is it Sunday?
>> I think Saturday means, yeah, Saturday.
>> Yeah, it's an online assessment, but it's a proctored test.
That means people observe you, then it's a closed book test.
So you're not allowed to refer to any other, what we call that,
resources during the test, yeah?
You have done this kind of test before?
>> Yes, Miss, for- >> The previous subject,
previous message subject, right?
>> Yeah, the mathematical one.
>> Okay, yeah, so let me share.
This is some important tips, so you just follow exactly.
So first of course, you need to understand on drawing ERD, okay?
So entity relationship diagram.
[BLANK_AUDIO]
So, I think we have done some studies before on drawing ERD diagram.
And for your test also, I think you've done ERD diagram, right?
So far, any of you still have any issues with ERD?
[BLANK_AUDIO]
So practice for, you can look for more example online.
I will try to check, is there any past year questions available?
Then I will try to share one set with question and answer.
So alert me, okay, maybe on Monday, I'll just look for
a sample questions, past year questions.
I'll share one set, so that you have more practice on
past year questions, you know, questions on past year papers.
And for second topic, it's about normalization.
Of course, normalization is a bit challenging topic compared to other topics here.
So here for your test, you need to understand UNF, unnormalized form.
And we have 1NF, 2NF, until the 3NF.
[BLANK_AUDIO]
Okay, so you'll be given a data set, or you'll be given another scenario.
So from there, you have to perform all this normalization, UNF until 3NF, okay?
So try to refer to the, for those who.